<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>IGN All</title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles</link><description>The latest IGN news, reviews and videos about video games, movies, TV, tech and comics</description><atom:link href="https://www.ign.com/rss/articles/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><atom:link href="https://www.ign.com/rss/articles/feed?start=20&amp;count=20" rel="next" type="application/rss+xml"/><image><url>https://s3.amazonaws.com/o.assets.images.ign.com/kraken/IGN-Logo-RSS.png</url><title>IGN Logo</title><link>https://www.ign.com</link><width>142</width><height>44</height></image><item><title><![CDATA[Blue Beetle Director and Star Respond to Backlash at ‘Batman’s a Fascist’ Line]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/blue-beetle-director-and-star-respond-to-backlash-at-batmans-a-fascist-line</link><description><![CDATA[Blue Beetle star Xolo Maridueña and director Ángel Manuel Soto have commented on the backlash to a line in the trailer when someone calls Batman "a fascist".]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 11:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">2342f622-6815-4f21-a917-de8c84188f3f</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>A line in the recent <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/dc-first-blue-beetle-trailer">Blue Beetle trailer</a> seems to have angered some DC fans. At one point, Uncle Rudy (played by George Lopez) calls Batman a “fascist” and while it’s a bit of a mic drop moment, some fans weren’t impressed.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>Now, director Ángel Manuel Soto and star Xolo Maridueña have responded. “We always wanted to have fun with the way Rudy talks about other superheroes,” said Soto. “So, to the people who got mad at it, give us a chance. We’re just trying to have fun with the characters that we love.”</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="blue-beetle-official-trailer" data-loop=""></section><p>“Everybody in our movie loves Batman and Superman and Flash,” he added. “And of course, we have criticisms about all of them, as we all should. But that doesn’t mean that we hate Batman. We love Batman.”</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/movies/blue-beetle-the-movie">Blue Beetle</a> stars Maridueña as Jaime Reyes, a teenage boy who finds himself bonded with a piece of alien technology that summons a powerful “world-destroying” weapon in the form of a high-tech armored suit.</p><p>He’s the latest DC hero to head to the big screen and will effectively kick off the DCU. However, Maridueña was a bit more direct with his response:</p><p>“F that! Maybe Jaime and the audience don’t agree with Rudy, but you’re allowed to have your opinion,” he said. “That’s okay… If you felt some type of way about it, that was the point. So, I think if you agree with it, if you don’t agree with it, it was placed there for a reason. And you know, all of the people who have their Batman shrines at home can keep them there and they don’t have to worry.”</p><p>The pair have previously <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/blue-beetle-first-latino-superhero-movie">discussed the film’s Latino roots</a>, calling Blue Beetle “unapologetically Latino”.</p><p>Blue Beetle debuts in theaters on August 18, 2023.</p><p>Want to read more about Blue Beetle? Find out <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/blue-beetle-explained-jaime-reyes-ted-kord-dcu">more about DC’s newest big-screen hero</a> and check out <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-blue-beetle-comics">our favourite Blue Beetle comics</a>.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Ryan Leston is an entertainment journalist and film critic for IGN. You can follow him on </em><a href="https://twitter.com/RyanLeston"><em>Twitter</em></a><em>.</em></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2022/12/03/blue-beetle-1660149833320-1670087339926.jpeg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Ryan Leston</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Internet Has a Lot of Opinions About Brad Pitt's Formula 1 Movie Car]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/internet-opinions-brad-pitt-formula-one-movie-car</link><description><![CDATA[Apple has rolled out a first look at Brad Pitt's Formula 1 movie car, and the internet has plenty to say about it.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 10:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">8d1cb977-e2e6-4986-8b84-42fbbed1da09</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Apple has rolled out a first look at Brad Pitt&#39;s Formula 1 movie car, and the internet has plenty to say about it.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>Pitt is gearing up to head out onto the race track to start filming between practice sessions at Silverstone during the British Grand Prix this weekend. Pitt is set to star alongside Damson Idris in the upcoming Formula 1 feature from Top Gun: Maverick director Joseph Kosinski.</p><p>In the movie, Pitt plays former F1 driver Sonny Hayes, who returns to racing in a bid to mentor a young racer to victory for the fictional APXGP team. Even at this early stage, it looks like his car has already gone for a spin as the official <a href="https://twitter.com/F1/status/1676878758974726144?s=20">F1 Twitter page</a> dropped an image of Pitt&#39;s new set of wheels.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">FIRST LOOK: Introducing APXGP, starring in an Apple Original Film<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/F1?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#F1</a> <a href="https://t.co/0qDe3zMicp">pic.twitter.com/0qDe3zMicp</a></p>&mdash; Formula 1 (@F1) <a href="https://twitter.com/F1/status/1676878758974726144?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>The car&#39;s ultra-sleek design features a striking black and gold color scheme, which has already caught the attention of spectators. Social media users were quick off the mark to share their verdict, and it sparked some interesting comparisons, with the resounding opinion being that it looks like &quot;a Duracell battery with wheels&quot;.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Wait a second…</p>&mdash; Duracell (@Duracell) <a href="https://twitter.com/Duracell/status/1676966319525347330?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="qme" dir="ltr"> <a href="https://t.co/mjY3BIx92M">pic.twitter.com/mjY3BIx92M</a></p>&mdash; HypeRate.io (@Hyperate_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/Hyperate_io/status/1676905582958194688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">They could have atleast made a nice livery instead of just making a duracell battery</p>&mdash; Luke Rogers (@saiint) <a href="https://twitter.com/saiint/status/1676879008363950081?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It&#39;s a Duracell Battery with wheels</p>&mdash; SENESCAL PERFUMADO (@okardahl) <a href="https://twitter.com/okardahl/status/1676881716223389696?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>However, some people flagged the vehicle&#39;s similarities to the Haas livery during its partnership with Rich Energy for the 2019 season, while others found the image fuelled their hype for the movie as they marvelled at the car&#39;s design and details.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Gene Haas walked so Brad Pitt could run <a href="https://t.co/owXc2nxZej">https://t.co/owXc2nxZej</a> <a href="https://t.co/uknKSkFot2">pic.twitter.com/uknKSkFot2</a></p>&mdash; Matt³³⁺¹⁶ | 🇬🇧SILVERSTONE🇬🇧 (@FM1_3316) <a href="https://twitter.com/FM1_3316/status/1676958242206011397?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">i zoomed in looking for the rich energy logo somewhere on it 😂😂</p>&mdash; 𝘫𝘢𝘴𝘦 (@betalogic) <a href="https://twitter.com/betalogic/status/1676882765260914688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Its like AliExpress made a Haas Rich Energy livery <a href="https://t.co/U115UwU4UX">pic.twitter.com/U115UwU4UX</a></p>&mdash; ThomasKebab (@TheThomasKebab) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheThomasKebab/status/1677095869445816321?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The way that this livery looks better than some of the real teams on the grid <a href="https://t.co/TYjs3gajqZ">https://t.co/TYjs3gajqZ</a></p>&mdash; Kev (@juicyfruitkev) <a href="https://twitter.com/juicyfruitkev/status/1677196000111497217?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 7, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This looks so 🔥</p>&mdash; Ankitä (@vitiligowoman) <a href="https://twitter.com/vitiligowoman/status/1676899204801654784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Wow, can&#39;t wait to see the new Apple Original Film featuring APXGP! Exciting times ahead! 🍿🎬</p>&mdash; F O R R E S T (@forrestlesch) <a href="https://twitter.com/forrestlesch/status/1676924646825009154?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>Kosinski previously shared he would be <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/top-gun-maverick-director-formula-1-movie-practical-effects">taking a practical approach to filming</a> the hotly anticipated Formula 1 movie rather than relying on CGI as a tool, following his success with Top Gun: Maverick and <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/how-top-gun-maverick-astonishing-practical-effects-were-achieved">its breathtaking in-camera flight sequences</a>.</p><p>&quot;Seeing people react to an in-camera, authentically captured film like Top Gun makes us all feel good that our approach works and is appreciated by audiences,&quot; he told <a href="https://www.thewrap.com/formula-one-joseph-kosinski-new-details/">The Wrap</a>. &quot;It&#39;s almost funny to me to see people who are so enamored with real photography. Younger people almost haven&#39;t seen a lot of it. They&#39;re so used to CGI being a tool of big movies that when you shoot something for real, it feels innovative.&quot;</p><p>Kosinski is collaborating on the untitled Formula 1 feature with writer Ehren Kruger, who also worked on the Top Gun sequel, and producer Jerry Bruckheimer. The movie will be released in theaters and run for at least 30 days before heading to the Apple TV+ streaming service.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Adele Ankers-Range is a freelance entertainment writer for IGN. </em><a href="https://twitter.com/AdeleAnkers"><em>Follow her on Twitter.</em></a></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/png" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/07/brad-pitt-formula-one-movie-first-look-1688720677779.png" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Adele Ankers-Range</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blizzard Pulls Diablo 4’s 6 Uber Unique Items After Apparently Making Them Too Easy to Get]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/blizzard-pulls-diablo-4s-6-uber-unique-items-after-apparently-making-them-too-easy-to-get</link><description><![CDATA[Blizzard has temporarily disabled Diablo 4’s six super rare unique items to address a new issue with Helltide Chest drops.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 10:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">2247a5f2-e0af-4011-b554-f9c279c1e44a</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Blizzard has temporarily disabled Diablo 4’s six super rare unique items from the game to address a new issue with Helltide Chest drops.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>The July 6 release of <a href="https://news.blizzard.com/en-us/diablo4/23964909/diablo-iv-patch-notes">update 1.0.4</a> added unique items to the Helltide Chest loot pool. Helltide Mystery Chests are special chests available from taking part in Helltide events. (For a more detailed look at the Mystery Chest locations check out our <a href="https://www.ign.com/maps/diablo-4/sanctuary"><u>Interactive Map</u></a>. You can filter Mystery Chest Locations at the bottom to clear some of the clutter.)</p><p>The change was welcomed by players on the hunt for <a href="https://www.ign.com/wikis/diablo-4/How_to_Get_the_Rarest_Unique_Items">Diablo 4’s rarest items</a>, such as the six super rare uniques currently in the game. <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/blizzard-confirms-diablo-4-has-six-super-rare-unique-items-sparks-debate-about-lottery-level-rarity">Fans had complained about the miniscule chance</a> to obtain them, with some comparing the drop rate to winning the lottery or getting struck by lightning. So the chance to obtain one super rare unique, however small, from a Helltide Chest gave players a clear, singular farming objective.</p><p>However, Blizzard abruptly disabled the super rare uniques from dropping in-game entirely to address an unnamed issue with Helltide Chest drops. “Players will not be able to obtain the six uber unique items until a hotfix which we expect to be implemented on Friday afternoon Pacific Time,” <a href="https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/d4/t/uber-unique-drops-temporarily-disabled-in-game/77799">Blizzard said</a>. “Other unique items will still be available from these chests.”</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="diablo-4-season-of-the-malignant-everything-you-need-to-know" data-loop=""></section><p>Blizzard has yet to explain the decision, but current speculation among fans is the developer noticed the six super rare uniques were dropping too frequently for its liking, and moved quickly to pull them from the game. The Harlequin Crest, aka the Shako, appears to have seen a dramatic drop rate improvement in particular.</p><p>“Yeah I couldn’t believe my eyes that I actually got one,” <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/diablo4/comments/14svadx/comment/jqzg7r6/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web3x&utm_name=web3xcss&utm_term=1&utm_content=share_button">said redditor HistoricalDuty3834</a>, who posted a picture of the Harlequin Crest on their character sheet. “I opened up a Helltide Chest with about 10 seconds left in it and was scrambling to take a pic for my friends I was playing with.”</p><p>Some Diablo 4 players reacted negatively to the move, accusing Blizzard of ruining their fun. “Fun police on patrol today,” <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/diablo4/comments/14svadx/comment/jqzaugv/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web3x&utm_name=web3xcss&utm_term=1&utm_content=share_button">said redditor loadsmoke</a>. “... so they genuinely only want like five of those to exist across the entire world?” <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/diablo4/comments/14svadx/comment/jqzb6hz/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web3x&utm_name=web3xcss&utm_term=1&utm_content=share_button">asked fkitbaylife</a>. </p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Please take this response as a sign that people actually want to have a chance to obtain these cool uniques. Even if it’s a 1% chance it’s still better than 0.0000001% chance.</p>&mdash; James (@jbsluggy) <a href="https://twitter.com/jbsluggy/status/1677179261457936385?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 7, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p></p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">People actually get the item to drop. NOPE NO MORE TOO MUCH OUT THERE. Were only allowed to have a handful worldwide. 😤 😂</p>&mdash; BigHeroSixy (@BigHeroSixy) <a href="https://twitter.com/BigHeroSixy/status/1677157106523185153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 7, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>Some players are now calling on Blizzard to rollback the Shakos obtained from Helltide Chests to prevent imbalance within the player-versus-player portion of Diablo 4. With a follow-up fix set to hit Diablo 4 soon, it won’t be long before super rare uniques are once again available to obtain from Helltide Chests, albeit with adjusted drop rates.</p><p>Diablo 4 launched big, becoming <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/diablo-4-is-blizzards-fastest-selling-game-of-all-time"><u>Blizzard’s fastest-selling game ever</u></a>. It is also <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/diablo-4-review"><u>a hit with critics</u></a>, and, generally, has gone down well with fans. However, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/now-diablo-4-is-out-in-the-wild-the-true-horror-of-its-costly-microtransactions-has-revealed-itself"><u>the cost of Diablo 4’s microtransactions has raised eyebrows</u></a>, and, surprisingly, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/whoopi-goldberg-really-wants-blizzard-to-release-diablo-4-on-mac"><u>Whoopi Goldberg called on Blizzard to release Diablo 4 on Mac</u></a>. Last night, Blizzard announced Diablo 4 Season 1, dubbed <a href="https://www.ign.com/videos/diablo-4-season-of-the-malignant-everything-you-need-to-know">Season of the Malignant</a>, starts July 20.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Wesley is the UK News Editor for IGN. Find him on Twitter at @wyp100. You can reach Wesley at </em><a href="mailto:jschreier10@bloomberg.net"><em>wesley_yinpoole@ign.com</em></a><em> or confidentially at </em><a href="mailto:jasonschreier@protonmail.com"><em>wyp100@proton.me.</em></a></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/06/10/diablo4ps5vsxboxseriesxsvspcperformancereview-36190303-diablo4-performancereview-blogroll-1686406111041.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Wesley Yin-Poole</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shang-Chi Star Gives Disappointing Sequel Update]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/shang-chi-star-gives-disappointing-sequel-update</link><description><![CDATA[Shang-Chi 2 star Simu Liu has revealed the upcoming Marvel sequel will follow the next Avengers movie, which "keeps pushing back".]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">83e28b2d-b2eb-461c-9e10-84806417b463</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/movies/shang-chi-and-the-legend-of-the-ten-rings">Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings</a> star Simu Liu has given a disappointing update about the upcoming sequel.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>During an AMA on Threads, the Marvel star confirmed <a href="https://www.ign.com/movies/shang-chi-and-the-legend-of-the-ten-rings-sequel">Shang-Chi 2</a> won’t head to the big screen anytime soon. “Was told it would follow Avengers,” he said. “But that keeps pushing back due to circumstances beyond my control. Hope to have more concrete news to share soon.”</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="shang-chi-the-full-story-of-the-mcus-mandarin" data-loop=""></section><p>The Avengers he mentioned is thought to be <a href="https://www.ign.com/movies/avengers-the-kang-dynasty">Avengers: Kang Dynasty</a>, the next big Avengers movie.</p><p>However, that film has seemingly hit a bit of a snag. Following claims of <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/new-report-on-jonathan-majors-alleges-almost-a-decade-of-abuse">abuse and toxic behavior from Kang star Jonathan Majors</a>, it’s unclear how Marvel intends to push forward with the upcoming Avengers flick. After all, in its earlier guise, the Avengers film would focus largely on Majors’ supervillain.</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/ant-man-3-writer-to-pen-avengers-the-kang-dynasty">Jeff Loveness is on scriptwriting duties</a> for Kang Dynasty, and director Destin Daniel Cretton will direct the movie. Cretton previously directed Shang-Chi and has been confirmed to <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/shang-chi-sequel-confirmed-destin-daniel-cretton">write and direct the upcoming sequel</a>.</p><p>However, while <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/shang-chi-2-sequel-destin-daniel-cretton">work had already begun on Shang-Chi 2</a>, it’s unclear how it will now forward, especially with Kang Dynasty’s fate up in the air.</p><p>“Going into a sequel feels exciting,” said Liu in <a href="https://comicbook.com/movies/news/marvels-simu-liu-teases-shang-chi-2-introducing-new-things-to-the-mcu/">an interview</a> earlier this year. “We&#39;re getting to revisit some things, but also show the viewer new things. We&#39;ll deliver all of the amazing action that we were celebrated for on the first movie, but then also hopefully explore new sides of Shaun&#39;s character and the characters around him. That is, of course, if we can still afford Michelle Yeoh. She&#39;s on top of the world and just the queen of everything.”</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/marvel-shang-chi-and-the-legend-of-the-ten-rings-review">IGN’s Shang-Chi review</a> gave it 8/10 and said: “Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings is a confident introduction to Marvel’s first Asian superhero, delivering the MCU’s best fight choreography and one of its most emotionally complex villains.”</p><p>Want to read more about Shang-Chi? Check out <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/shang-chi-2-jackie-chan-marvel-mcu">which iconic martial artist</a> the Shang-Chi 2 director wants in the sequel as well as <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/simu-liu-reveals-why-shang-chi-wears-air-jordans">why Shang-Chi wears Air Jordans</a>.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Ryan Leston is an entertainment journalist and film critic for IGN. You can follow him on </em><a href="https://twitter.com/RyanLeston"><em>Twitter</em></a><em>.</em></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="1080" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2021/12/03/shang-chi-blog-2-1618839388346-1638530060733.jpg" width="1920"/><dc:creator>Ryan Leston</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon Musk Accuses Meta of 'Cheating' With Twitter Rival Threads]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/elon-musk-accuses-meta-of-cheating-with-twitter-rival-threads</link><description><![CDATA[Twitter owner Elon Musk has accused Meta of “cheating” with the launch of rival social network Threads. Meta has denied the claim.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 09:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">4a0e52dd-505e-4886-a996-010d6da773f6</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Twitter owner Elon Musk has accused Meta of “cheating” with the launch of rival social network Threads.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>Twitter threatened to sue Meta over &quot;systematic, willful and unlawful misappropriation&quot; of Twitter&#39;s trade secrets and intellectual property, as well as scraping of Twitter&#39;s data, in a cease-and-desist letter sent to Mark Zuckerberg by Musk’s lawyer Alex Spiro. The letter was first reported by <a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/07/06/2023/twitter-is-threatening-to-sue-meta-over-threads">Semafor</a>.</p><p>In the legal letter, Spiro claimed ex-Twitter staff helped create the &quot;copycat&quot; Threads app. In an interview with the <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-65248196">BBC</a> in April, Musk said Twitter had laid off more than 6,000 employees, around 80% of its workforce, following his $44 billion purchase of the company. “Competition is fine, cheating is not,” Musk said in a tweet. Meta has denied the claims.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Competition is fine, cheating is not</p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1677042708756439041?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>Threads, which launched this week and already has more than 30 million users, is pitched as a “friendly” alternative to Twitter. Twitter currently has an estimated 350 million users.</p><p>Twitter’s letter is a legal threat only, and it has yet to file a lawsuit. According to the <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-66129215">BBC</a>, for Twitter to be successful in any legal claim, it would have to prove its own intellectual property, such as programming code, was taken and used without permission.</p><p>In the letter, Spiro accuses Meta of hiring dozens of former Twitter employees who &quot;had and continue to have access to Twitter&#39;s trade secrets and other highly confidential information&quot;.</p><p>&quot;Twitter intends to strictly enforce its intellectual property rights, and demands that Meta take immediate steps to stop using any Twitter trade secrets or other highly confidential information,&quot; the letter says.</p><p>&quot;Twitter reserves all rights, including, but not limited to, the right to seek both civil remedies and injunctive relief without further notice.&quot;</p><p>On <a href="https://www.threads.net/t/CuXeGudAEXr/?igshid=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ%3D%3D">Threads</a>, Meta spokesperson Andy Stone said &quot;no one on the Threads engineering team is a former Twitter employee - that&#39;s just not a thing&quot;.</p><p>With a new social media app for people to join, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/metas-twitter-competitor-is-here-what-the-internet-is-saying-about-threads">the internet has been vocal</a> about how they feel about Meta&#39;s new internet endeavor. The launch of Threads also sparked Zuckerberg&#39;s first tweet in 11 years.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="zxx" dir="ltr"><a href="https://t.co/MbMxUWiQgp">pic.twitter.com/MbMxUWiQgp</a></p>&mdash; Mark Zuckerberg (@finkd) <a href="https://twitter.com/finkd/status/1676747594460962817?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Image credit: Bloomberg / Getty Images<br />Wesley is the UK News Editor for IGN. Find him on Twitter at @wyp100. You can reach Wesley at </em><a href="mailto:jschreier10@bloomberg.net"><em>wesley_yinpoole@ign.com</em></a><em> or confidentially at </em><a href="mailto:jasonschreier@protonmail.com"><em>wyp100@proton.me.</em></a></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="683" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/07/gettyimages-1258889024-1688723385810.jpg" width="1024"/><dc:creator>Wesley Yin-Poole</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sonic Co-Creator Yuji Naka Given Suspended Prison Sentence for Insider Trading]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/sonic-co-creator-yuji-naka-given-suspended-prison-sentence-for-insider-trading</link><description><![CDATA[Yuji Naka, co-creator of the Sonic the Hedgehog series and former boss of Sonic Team at Sega, was given a  suspended prison sentence for insider trading following a trial in Japan.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">738455bd-4c9e-4a06-b7f8-c304ee64a8b4</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Yuji Naka, co-creator of the Sonic the Hedgehog series and former boss of Sonic Team at Sega, was given a  suspended prison sentence for insider trading following a trial in Japan.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>According to <a href="https://jp.ign.com/games/69028/news/">IGN Japan</a>, 57-year-old Naka was found guilty of violating Japan’s Financial Instruments and Exchange Act for insider trading in connection with the development of a game for publisher Square Enix.</p><p>Following a trial held at the Tokyo District Court on July 7, 2023, Judge Madoka Hiruta issued a two-and-a-half year prison sentence, suspended for four years, as well as two fines of ¥2 million ($14,000 approx) and ¥170 million ($1.1 million approx).</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="balan-wonderworld-review" data-loop=""></section><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/sonic-the-hedgehog-co-creator-yuji-naka-arrested-insider-trading-dragon-quest">Naka was arrested in November</a> for suspected insider trading relating to an investment made while working at Square Enix. He allegedly bought 10,000 shares in developer Aiming, at a value of around $20,000, ahead of the announcement of the <a href="https://www.ign.com/videos/dragon-quest-tact-dragon-quest-iv-event-trailer">Dragon Quest Tact mobile game</a> in partnership with Square Enix.</p><p>Insider trading is the buying and selling of stocks with confidential or non-public information, usually with the intention to make money, and is illegal in Japan.</p><p>Issuing the ruling, Judge Hiruta said: &quot;He was known as one of the world&#39;s most famous game developers, and had the authority to access joint development information. It has damaged the fairness and soundness of the stock market and the trust of investors.&quot;</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/sonic-the-hedgehog-vc-review"><u>Naka is arguably most known for co-creating Sonic the Hedgehog</u></a> and leading Sega&#39;s Sonic Team, but was also lead programmer on other games including Nights into Dreams, Phantasy Star Online, and more. He eventually joined Square Enix but left in June 2021, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/yuji-naka-square-enix-lawsuit-balan-wonderworld"><u>not long after the release of his latest game Balan Wonderland</u></a>.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Wesley is the UK News Editor for IGN. Find him on Twitter at @wyp100. You can reach Wesley at </em><a href="mailto:jschreier10@bloomberg.net"><em>wesley_yinpoole@ign.com</em></a><em> or confidentially at </em><a href="mailto:jasonschreier@protonmail.com"><em>wyp100@proton.me.</em></a></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/07/yuji-naka-1688720750391.jpg" width="1279"/><dc:creator>Wesley Yin-Poole</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[IGN x Activision – Crash Team Rumble Retweet Competition Terms & Conditions]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/ign-x-activision-crash-team-rumble-retweet-competition-terms-conditions</link><description/><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 08:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">0de428a8-533f-4db0-a930-a0ab97e9d0d3</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Ziff Davis International Ltd.</p><p>GAME OF CHANCE PROMOTION</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>TERMS AND CONDITIONS
</p><p>1. By participating in the Crash Team Rumble Retweet Competition (the &quot;Promotion&quot;) promoted by Ziff Davis International Ltd. (the &quot;Promoter&quot;), you agree to these Official Terms &amp; Conditions (the “Terms and Conditions”). When you enter the Promotion, these Terms and Conditions become a contract between you and the Promoter, so read them carefully before participating. This contract includes, without limitation, an indemnification by you of the released parties listed below and a limitation of your rights and remedies.
</p><p>2. The promoter of the Promotion is Ziff Davis International Ltd., 18 Mansell Street, London, E1 8AA (the “Promoter”). The sponsor of the Promotion is Activision (the “Sponsor”)</p><p></p><p>3. Entry is open to users who are legally resident in the United Kingdom and are eighteen (18) years of age or over. Entrants who are eligible to enter the Promotion pursuant to these Terms and Conditions are referred to as “Eligible Entrants”.</p><p></p><p>4. Directors, management, employees and officers of the Promoter and its related corporate entities (such as parent and subsidiary companies), as well as employees of associated agencies involved in the Promotion and their immediate families are ineligible to enter this Promotion. All previous winners of any Promotion promoted by Promoter during the nine (9) month period prior to the Selection Date are not eligible to enter. Any individuals (including, but not limited to, employees, consultants, independent contractors and interns) who have, within the past six (6) months, held employment with or performed services for Promoter or any organizations affiliated with the sponsorship, fulfilment, administration, prize support, advertisement or promotion of the Promotion (“Employees”) are not eligible to enter or win. Immediate Family Members and Household Members are also not eligible to enter or win. “Immediate Family Members” means parents, step-parents, legal guardians, children, step-children, siblings, step-siblings, or spouses of an Employee. “Household Members” means those individuals who share the same residence with an Employee at least three (3) months a year.</p><p></p><p>5. The Promotion commences 11:00AM (GMT) on 7 July 2023, and closes at 11:00AM (GMT) on 14 July, 2023 (the &quot;Promotion Period”).</p><p></p><p>6. To enter the Promotion, entrants have a Twitter account. To create a Twitter account, go to<a href="https://twitter.com/signup"> <u>https://twitter.com/signup</u></a>, fill out the form and click “sign up.” To enter the Promotion, entrants log into their Twitter account during the Promotion Period and retweet the below message at @IGNUK. Subsequent attempts made by the same individual to submit multiple entries by using multiple accounts or otherwise may result in disqualification of the entrant.</p><p></p><p><em>Let&#39;s get ready to #CrashTeamRumble! To celebrate the release of the new @CrashBandicoot 4v4 online multiplayer game, we&#39;re giving away 10 digital Deluxe Editions for PS4/5, plus 2 Crash statues. Retweet for a chance to win! / UK 18+ #ad / T&amp;Cs: [LINK]</em></p><p><em></em></p><p>Entries submitted by any other means than as described above will not be accepted. Any illegible, incomplete or fraudulent entries will be rejected. Only one entry per person will be accepted. Use of script, macro or any automated system to enter the Promotion is prohibited and entries made (or which appear to have been made, in Promotor’s sole discretion) using any such system may be treated as void. All entries become the property of the Promoter. Participants must follow the directions provided by the Promoter and otherwise be bound by and follow these Terms and Conditions to be eligible to receive a Prize in connection with the Promotion. Participants may not take actions that are negligent, injurious or reckless in pursuit of any prize offered in connection with the Promotion. Participants who do not follow this rule or who otherwise participate in the Promotion in an unsportsmanlike manner will be disqualified from the Promotion. Participants alone are responsible for any injuries or other damages that are caused or incurred as a result of their behavior.</p><p></p><p>7. The winning entries will be selected by random drawing or other randomized process on or around 17 July 2023 (the “Selection Date”) from all complete, eligible, properly submitted entries received by the Promoter during the Promotion Period. The ten entrants whose entries are drawn from the eligible entries shall win the Prize as described below. The first two winners shall be considered the “Grand Prize” winners. The remaining eight winners will be considered “Runner Ups” and receive a different prize from the Grand Prize Winners There will be only ten prize recipients for this Promotion. This is a game of chance and skill plays no part in determining the Prize Winner. The Prize Winners will be notified by Twitter direct message on or around 17 July 2023. If the Prize Winners do not reply to the notification acknowledging acceptance of the Prize within one business day, such Prize Winners may forfeit the Prize. In such instance, the Promoter reserves the right to award the Prize to another Eligible Entrant.</p><p></p><p>8. Promoter will determine the Prize Winners in its sole and absolute discretion in accordance with these Terms and Conditions. If any Prize Winner is determined to be ineligible to receive the Prize, Promoter may, in its sole and absolute discretion, not give away the goods or may give the goods to the next runner up. If you are selected as a Prize Winner, you will be required to privately (e.g., by email or other secure, private means) provide your name, address, age and other personal information necessary to receive the Prize. The name, contact number and address of the Prize Winner will be passed to a third party provider for delivery. Except for Winner Information (defined below), Promoter will not keep or store your information or use it for any purpose other than sending the Prize or providing you information on receiving the Prize. Promotions are subject to all applicable laws, rules or regulations and these Terms and Conditions.</p><p></p><p>9. There will be ten winners (each a “Prize Winner”) for the Promotion who will receive the following prize (the “Prize”):</p><p>Two Grand Prize Winners will receive</p><p>1x digital copy of the Deluxe Edition of Crash Team Rumble, including;</p><ul><li>Crash Team Rumble™ for PS4™/PS5™</li><li>Season 1 Premium Battle Pass</li><li>Season 2 Premium Battle Pass</li><li>25 Tier Unlock for S1</li><li>Digital Proto Pack</li></ul><p>(RRP £24.99)</p><p>1 x Crash Bandicoot™ 9&quot; PVC Painted Crash statue (RRP $95.99/approx. £75.50)</p><p>Eight Runner Up winners will receive:</p><p>1x digital copy of the Deluxe Edition of Crash Team Rumble, including;</p><ul><li>Crash Team Rumble™ for PS4™/PS5™</li><li>Season 1 Premium Battle Pass</li><li>Season 2 Premium Battle Pass</li><li>25 Tier Unlock for S1</li><li>Digital Proto Pack</li></ul><p>(RRP £24.99)</p><p></p><p>10. The Prize must be accepted by the Prize Winner as stated and cannot be transferred to another person, exchanged for other goods and services or redeemed as cash in whole or in part. Any element of a Prize which is not accepted will be forfeited, and no compensation will be paid in lieu of that element of the Prize. Should a Prize be unavailable at the time that the Promoter seeks to acquire the Prize for the Prize Winner, Promoter reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to substitute with an alternative of equal or greater value or to substitute a cash alternative for any Prize. The Promoter accepts no responsibility for any variation of the Prize or any aspect of the Prize due to circumstances outside its reasonable control. You agree that the Prize is awarded on an “as is” basis and that neither the Promoter nor any of its parents, subsidiaries or affiliated companies make any representations or warranties of any nature with respect to the Prize. Each Prize Winner in the Promotion is solely responsible for any and all applicable taxes (including income and withholding taxes on any Prize), regardless of whether the Prize, in whole or in part, is used. The actual retail value of any Prize is based on available information provided to the Promoter and the value of any Prize awarded to a Prize Winner must be reported for tax purposes as required by law. Prizes may be subject to the terms and conditions of a third party prize provider which will be made available by such third party; in such instance, any complaints or queries relating to the use of the Prize should be directed to such third party prize provider.</p><p></p><p>11. Except for any liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence, fraud or any other liability that cannot be excluded by law, the Promoter and its parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliated companies, units and divisions, and the current and former officers, directors, employees, shareholders, agents, successors and assigns of each of the foregoing, and all those acting under the authority of the foregoing or any of them (including, but not limited to, advertising and promotional agencies and prize suppliers) (collectively, the &quot;Released Parties&quot;) exclude all liability, claims, actions, injury, loss, damages, liabilities and obligations of any kind whatsoever (collectively, “Claims”), whether known or unknown, suspected or unsuspected, which entrants have ever had, now have, or hereafter can, shall or may have, against the Released Parties (or any of them), including, but not limited to, all Claims for personal injury, theft, unauthorised access or third party interference arising from or related to: (a) the Promotion; and (b) the receipt, ownership, use, transfer, sale or other disposition of the Prize, including, but not limited to, claims for personal injury, death, and/or property damages. Prize Winner shall be solely responsible for any tax liability incurred in connection with the Prize.</p><p></p><p>12. The Promoter accepts no responsibility for any variation of the Prize or any aspect of the Prize, due to circumstances outside its reasonable control. In any such event, an alternative prize or element of the Prize will be arranged. The Promoter is not responsible for any problem or technical malfunction of any website or communications network or any late, lost, incorrectly submitted, delayed, ineligible, incomplete, corrupted or misdirected entry whether due to error, transmission interruption or otherwise. The Promoter reserves the right to disqualify any entrant submitting an entry which, in the opinion of the Promoter, includes objectionable content, including but not limited to profanity, nudity, potentially insulting, scandalous, inflammatory or defamatory images or language. The Promoter’s decision is final.</p><p></p><p>13. If, for any reason, the Promotion is not capable of running as planned, including, but not limited to, infection by computer virus, bugs, tampering, unauthorised intervention, fraud, technical failures or any other causes beyond the reasonable control of the Promoter which corrupt or affect the administration security, fairness, integrity or proper conduct of this Promotion, the Promoter reserves the right in its sole discretion to disqualify any individual who tampers with the entry process, and/or to cancel, terminate, modify or suspend the Promotion. The Promoter assumes no responsibility for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorised access to, or alteration of, entries beyond its reasonable control. The Promoter is not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of any entry to be received by the Promoter on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website, or any combination thereof, including any injury or damage to participant&#39;s or any other person&#39;s computer related to or resulting from participation or downloading any materials in this Promotion. CAUTION: ANY ATTEMPT TO DELIBERATELY DAMAGE ANY WEBSITE OR THE INFORMATION ON A WEBSITE, OR TO OTHERWISE UNDERMINE THE LEGITIMATE OPERATION OF THIS PROMOTION, MAY BE A VIOLATION OF CRIMINAL AND CIVIL LAWS AND SHOULD SUCH AN ATTEMPT BE MADE, WHETHER SUCCESSFUL OR NOT, THE PROMOTER RESERVES THE RIGHT TO SEEK DAMAGES TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.</p><p></p><p>14. The Prize Winner, by acceptance of the Prize, grants to Promoter and its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, designees and assigns the right to publicize his or her name, address (city and country of residence), photograph, voice, statements and/or other likeness and prize information for advertising, promotional and/or trade and/or any other purpose (&quot;Winner Information&quot;) in any media or format now known or hereafter devised, throughout the world, in perpetuity, without limitation and without further compensation, consideration, permission or notification, except where prohibited by law. The Prize Winner agrees to participate in reasonable publicity activities surrounding the Promotion as requested by the Promoter.</p><p></p><p>15. These Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of England and Wales. The courts located in London, England shall have exclusive jurisdiction to hear any dispute or claim arising in association with the Promotion or these Terms and Conditions.</p><p></p><p>16. Without limiting the foregoing, the personal information provided by entrants in connection with this Promotion will be handled in accordance with data protection legislation and in accordance with the Promoter’s privacy policy, which may be found<a href="https://www.ziffdavis.com/privacy-policy"> <u>here</u></a>. You understand that when you register on the Twitter website or submit information to or via Twitter, such submissions are also subject to Twitter’s privacy policy.</p><p></p><p>17. Although the Promotion may be featured on Twitter, Facebook and/or other social media platforms, the Promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed, administered by, or association with Twitter, Facebook and/or such other social media platforms and you agree that Twitter, Facebook and all other social media platforms are not liable in any way for any claims, damages or losses associated with the Promotion.</p><p>18. A list of Promotion winners can be made available on request by writing after the selection date to the offices of the Promoter: Ziff Davis International Ltd., 18 Mansell Street, London, E1 8AA. A stamped addressed envelope must be included with the request.</p><p>BY ENTERING, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND AGREE TO ALL OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.</p><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><dc:creator>Alison Rowley</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should You Buy a Gaming PC on Amazon Prime Day 2023?]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/should-you-buy-a-gaming-pc-deal-on-amazon-prime-day-2023</link><description><![CDATA[More gaming PC deals are on their way next week, here's what to expect.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 01:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">158086a9-44a9-4bbc-ad6a-4f43d656b405</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>If you’re looking to obtain a new gaming PC on Amazon Prime Day this year, then you have two different options available. You can either purchase the components, including a GPU, to make your own gaming PC or you can go prebuilt. Many of the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-gaming-pc"><u>best prebuilt gaming PCs</u></a> come packing plenty of power to play even the most intensive <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-pc-games"><u>PC games</u></a>, but there are also quite a few <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-budget-gaming-pc"><u>budget gaming PCs</u></a> that can still run popular new titles.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>Although Prime Day doesn’t always feature the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-gaming-pc-deals"><u>best gaming PC deals</u></a> of all time, it’s still a great time to find discounts on popular brands like Alienware, Acer, HP, Cyberpower, and Corsair if you know what you’re looking for. Prime Day gaming PC deals will begin on July 11 and run through July 12 with the rest of the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/amazon-prime-day-2023-dates-announced"><u>best Prime Day deals</u></a>.</p><h2>What Gaming PC Deals Should You Expect on Amazon Prime Day?</h2><a href="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2022/02/15/gamingpc-1644948140778.jpg"><img src="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2022/02/15/gamingpc-1644948140778.jpg" class="article-image-full-size"/></a><p>Although there are likely to be some discounts on gaming PCs with 40 series GPUs, the best Prime Day gaming PC deals will likely be on prebuilt desktops with 30 series GPUs. We may not know what specific models and configurations will go on sale during Prime Day, but we do know that some brands have traditionally been discounted during the summer sales events.</p><p>The two brands that tend to offer some of the best prices are iBUYPOWER and CyberPowerPC. Both of these brands will likely have some sort of offering with an RTX 30 series GPU for under $1,000 as well as older models for under $800. Additionally, we usually see pretty good discounts on various HP Omen builds and Alienware Auroras. There are almost always <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/the-best-dell-alienware-deals-and-coupons-gaming-laptops-pcs-monitors-and-more"><u>Dell and Alienware deals</u></a>, but more often that not they are on the higher-end PCs available, so Prime Day sales are a good time to find discounts on more budget configurations.</p><p>You will likely also find quite a few deals on gaming PCs for under $500 or even under $300, but these low price points are often for machines that won’t be able to properly run newer PC games. Make sure to check the specs before you make a purchase.</p><h3>Do Other Retailers Have Gaming PC Deals on Prime Day?</h3><p>When it comes to gaming desktops, Amazon isn’t the only retailer that offers discounts during its summer sales event. Walmart will offer a counter sale that will have some configurations available, but the best places to look for discounts or tech-focused retailers. The Best Buy Black Friday in July sale will be a great place to look for discounted gaming PCs, and Newegg has also announced its own sale to rival Amazon Prime Day.</p><p>Outside of the major retailers, the manufacturer’s websites are also a great place to find deals directly from the source. Dell, HP, and Lenovo all have discounts available and will likely continue to cycle through various coupons and deals on different configurations throughout Prime Day. The <a href="https://ign.com/articles/dell-black-friday-in-july-sale-alienware-gaming-laptops-and-pcs">Dell Black Friday in July sale</a> is even already live.</p><h2>Should You Buy a Gaming PC on Prime Day or Black Friday?</h2><p>Although discounts on PCs do tend to fluctuate depending on the season, the biggest factor in gaming pc prices tends to be the components themselves. So it’s hard to say whether or not you should buy now or wait until later. That being said, GPU prices have mostly normalized and right now is a surprisingly good time to invest in a gaming PC compared to previous years.</p><p>If you find a decent gaming PC for less that $800 that packs an RTX 3060, then it’s probably worth pulling the trigger on. We are still a ways off from the next generation of GPUs and 2023 has been a great year for games so far, so now is a good time to upgrade your setup.</p><h3>Early Prime Day Gaming PC Deals</h3><p>Although Prime Day hasn&#39;t arrived yet, there are already plenty of good gaming PC deals to go around. Here are some of the best discounts right now:</p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-alienware-gaming-pcs-evergreen" data-type="grid"></section></p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p>Trying to decide between a <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/gaming-laptop-vs-gaming-pc">gaming PC and a gaming laptop</a>? Check out the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-gaming-laptop-deals">best gaming laptop deals</a> going on right now.
</p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/02/10/021023-1676065862447.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Jacob Kienlen</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sega Executive Dismisses 'Play-to-Earn' Blockchain Games as 'Boring']]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/sega-executive-dismisses-play-to-earn-blockchain-games-as-boring</link><description><![CDATA[Sega was initially on board with blockchain gaming technology but has now started to pull away from it as the technology hadn't taken off as expected.]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 00:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">857d0c01-365d-4303-be77-647d39338f70</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Sega isn&#39;t as all in on blockchain gaming as it was before, now withholding its biggest IP such as Sonic the Hedgehog from being used in third-party blockchain games. This move is to ensure that Sega doesn&#39;t devalue its own content.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>Speaking with <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-06/sega-joins-blockchain-games-pullback-as-crypto-winter-persists">Bloomberg</a>, Sega co-chief operating officer Shuji Utsumi panned blockchain games as &quot;boring.&quot;</p><p>&quot;The action in play-to-earn games is boring. What’s the point if games are no fun?&quot; Utsumi said.</p><p>However, Sega will still let external partners use characters from lesser known franchises such as Three Kingdoms and Virtua Fighter as NFTs. Utsumi noted that the technology remains useful in instances where it&#39;s possible to move characters and items between different games.</p><p>Sega is also pausing its own blockchain gaming projects for now and being indecisive about implemetning Web3 technology in its <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/sega-microsoft-strategic-alliance">upcoming suite of &quot;super games.&quot;</a></p><section data-transform="quoteBox">The action in play-to-earn games is boring. What’s the point if games are no fun?</section><p>However, Sega is still open to using blockchain techology if it ever does become successful, as Utsumi said that the audience shouldn&#39;t doubt risk-takers. </p><p>&quot;For the majority of people in the video game industry, what blockchain advocates say may sound a bit extreme, but that’s how the first penguin has always been,&quot; Utsumi explained. &quot;We should never underestimate them.&quot;</p><p>Blockchain gaming has been a controversial topic over the past few years. Many companies jumped onto the trend, including <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/square-enix-nft-blockchain-web3-elixir">Square</a> Enix and <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/ubisoft-quartz-announced-blockchain-nfts-digits-cosmetics">Ubisoft</a>. However, many gamers weren&#39;t fond of this. More companies have also dismissed blockchain gaming after it hadn&#39;t taken off as high as expected. Electronic Arts initially spoke positively about blockchain gaming but then later stated it wasn&#39;t <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/ea-not-driving-hard-direction-nfts">&quot;driving hard&quot;</a> in that direction anymore.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>George Yang is a freelance writer for IGN. He&#39;s been writing about the industry since 2019 and has worked with other publications such as Insider, Kotaku, NPR, and Variety.</em></p><p><em>When not writing about video games, George is playing video games. What a surprise! You can follow him on Twitter @Yinyangfooey</em></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="1080" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/06/08/sonicthumb-1686253410260.jpg" width="1920"/><dc:creator>George Yang</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capcom Is Considering New Mega Man Games, It Just Needs Some Ideas]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/capcom-is-considering-new-mega-man-games-it-just-needs-some-ideas</link><description><![CDATA[Capcom says that it's considering how to approach future games in the Mega Man series, potentially signaling a shift for the classic franchise.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 23:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">b289138c-1fd2-4eb6-a260-9ce0c9252867</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Mega Man has a long and storied video game history. Even Capcom thinks so. </p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>In a recent shareholder&#39;s meeting, the publisher called the series &quot;one of Capcom&#39;s historic franchises&quot; and noted that it&#39;s &quot;loved by fans.&quot; Since the departure of series designer Keiji Inafune, though, Mega Man&#39;s appearances have been few and far between, with the Blue Bomber last appearing in a mainline game in 2018, and Mega Man X&#39;s last major console outing being in 2005.</p><p><section data-transform="poll" data-id="91ac3168-53ae-4d54-af92-da48a918e0f4"></section></p><p>But take heart, Mega Man fans. Capcom says that it&#39;s still thinking about the future of the series, and that also includes older favorites like Sengoku Basara and Onimusha. </p><p>&quot;We are considering how to approach the production of new entries in the series, which requires numerous factors, including the development of a solid concept, ideas and gameplay, etc,&quot; Capcom says.</p><p>Capcom&#39;s comments follow the release of Mega Man Battle Network Legacy Collection, which has managed to surpass 1 million units sold since its release back in April. Capcom also showed Mega Man X Dive Offline at the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/capcom-showcase-2023-everything-announced">recent Capcom Showcase</a>, which is planned for release on Steam, iOS, and Android.</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="mega-man-11-review" data-loop=""></section><p>Mega Man&#39;s storied history stretches back to the days of the NES, where it helped to establish Capcom as a major player on the platform. In the years that followed, Capcom released many more entries in the series plus a host of spin-offs, leading some to complain that there were <em>too many</em> Mega Man games.</p><p>Inafune departed Capcom in 2010, leading to the cancellation of multiple projects, including the much-anticipated Mega Man Legends 3. Since then, Mega Man has primarily been seen in retro collections and mobile titles, with the biggest exception being the moderately well-received Mega Man 11. As for Inafune, his attempt to recreate the magic of Mega Man with Mighty No. 9 <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2016/06/20/mighty-no-9-review">was famously a bust.</a></p><p>In the meantime, Capcom is gearing up to release Exoprimal, its new multiplayer game pitting humans in exosuits against dinsaurs. Its due July 14.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Kat Bailey is IGN&#39;s News Director as well as co-host of Nintendo Voice Chat. Have a tip? Send her a DM at @the_katbot.</em></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="1080" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets1.ignimgs.com/2018/09/15/switch-megaman11-screen-5-bounce-weapon-1536971345133.jpg" width="1920"/><dc:creator>Kat Bailey</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Deals: PS5 DualSense Edge, Kindle Unlimited, Walmart+, AMD Radeon RX 7900 XTX GPU, AMD Ryzen 9 7950X3D CPU, and More]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/daily-deals-july-06-2023</link><description/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">55227b9d-728d-45d5-a5e2-13e9003e4642</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Today&#39;s daily deals for Thursday, July 6 include free Amazon credit, a free Dell egift card when you purchase a PS5 DualSense Edge premium controller, 50% off 1 year of Walmart+ (and you get Paramount+ as well), 3 free months of Kindle Unlimited, great deals on top-end AMD CPUs and GPUs, and more.</p><h3>Buy $50 Amazon eGift Card, Get Free $5 Amazon Credit</h3><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><em><strong>Amazon Prime members only</strong></em></p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-prime-day" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>From July 3 to July 10, Amazon is offering <a href="https://zdcs.link/gLBJq">free $5 in Amazon credit</a> when you purchase a $50 Amazon eGift card. If you buy a digital gift card, you&#39;ll receive it almost immediately via email. The bonus $5 credit should be automatically added to your Amazon account within minutes of making your gift card purchase.</p><p>There are a couple of caveats to this deal. You have to be an Amazon Prime member and be logged into your account to see this deal. You will also have to use your credit <strong>by August 23, 2023</strong>. Fortunately, because you will receive the credit almost immediately, you can apply it to any Prime Day purchases you make. That&#39;s pretty awesome because we often see cashback deals from other vendors with a time freeze associated with them, so you can&#39;t actually use the funds until after a certain big sale has passed.</p><h3>PS5 DualSense Edge Controller for $199.99 Plus Bonus $75 Dell eGift Card</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-ps5-dualsense-edge" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Dell is offering a bonus $75 Dell eGift Card when you purchase a <a href="https://zdcs.link/2XXp5">PS5 DualSense Edge</a> controller for $199.99. That&#39;s easily the best deal we&#39;ve ever seen for this premium controller. The promotional gift card will be sent to your inbox within 20 days and you&#39;ll have 90 days thereafter to spend it. You can use it on pretty much anything at Dell.com, including gaming PCs and laptops, monitors, gaming consoles and video games, electronics, and more. The DualSense Edge is Sony&#39;s high-end controller for the PS5 console. Like the Xbox Elite Series 2 controller, it offers pro-level features like grips, adjustable analog sticks, mappable rear buttons, profiles, and more.</p><h3>Gigabyte AMD Radeon RX 7900 XTX 24GB OC GPU for $899.99</h3><p><em><strong>Better than an RTX 4080</strong></em></p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-amd-radeon-rx-7900-xtx" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>The Radeon RX 7900 XTX is AMD&#39;s flagship card, and it&#39;s mean enough to challenge the crazy powerful GeForce RTX 40 series cards. In fact, it outperforms the $1199 GeForce RTX 4080 in most games. It&#39;s also a good candidate for 3D work because of its higher amount of VRAM (24GB vs 18GB). The RTX 4080 does win out on ray tracing and DLSS performance, but that&#39;s a pretty awesome win for a card that&#39;s currently selling for $899.99 on Amazon right now, or $300 less than a 4080.</p><h3>Early Prime Day Deal: Get 3 Months of Kindle Unlimited for Free</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-kindle-unlimited" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Along with <a href="https://zdcs.link/GYDjx">Audible</a> and <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/amazon-prime-day-music-unlimited-membership-deal">Amazon Music</a>, there&#39;s now a freebie Kindle deal. Right now new subscribers can get 3 months of Kindle Unlimited for free. Kindle Unlimited normally costs about $11.99 per month, so you&#39;re saving over $35. With a Kindle Unlimited membership, you’ll have unlimited access to both digital titles and audiobooks. There are actually millions of comics, books, magazines, and more on Kindle Unlimited - it&#39;s absolutely nuts what you can find to read at zero cost to you right now. From Marvel and DC comic volumes to Batman, Star Wars, and The Witcher, alongside popular magazines like Total Film, Empire, Men&#39;s Health, Four Four Two, SFX, Edge, and more. It&#39;s quite clear that Unlimited packs a lot.</p><h3>50% Off 1 Year of Walmart+</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-walmart" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Walmart has decided to counter Amazon Prime Day with a week long bevy of deals for Walmart+ memberls, Unlike Amazon Prime Day, this even starts now. The biggest deal right now is on Walmart+ itself, which is being offered for $49 for the first year (normally $99). The Walmart+ subscription gives you access to free shipping, free store delivery, and free return pickup. As an extra perk, you also get a Paramount+ subscription for the duration of your W+ subscription.</p><h3>AMD Ryzen 9 7950X3D 16-Core 32-Thread AM5 Desktop CPU for $557</h3><p><em><strong>The best gaming CPU on the market</strong></em></p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-amd-ryzen-9-7950x3d" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>The AMD Ryzen 9 7950X3D sees a rather significant discount today. It&#39;s normally $699, but there&#39;s a $70 instant discount that be be combined with a $72.99 coupon you can clip on the product page.  This is currently the <strong>best </strong>gaming CPU out there right now. Thanks to the boost from AMD&#39;s 3D V-Cache technology, it powers past both the AMD Ryzen 9 7950 and the Intel Core i9-13900K when it comes to gaming performance, and it&#39;s also more power efficient than its Intel competition. It&#39;s also based off the socket AM5 platform, which is going to be around for many years to come (unlike recent Intel sockets, which only have a shelf-life of a few years).</p><h3>New 2023 55&quot; Hisense U8K 4K Mini LED TV for $799.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-hisense-u8k" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Hisense recently released the updated 2023 model of its highest end TV, the U8 series.Like the 2022 U8H, the new 2023 U8K boasts a Mini-LED panel with quantum dot technology (QLED) and wide color gamut (ULED). Mini LED panels allow for even more precise dimming because the controller zones are smaller and more numerous. Not all Mini-LED panels are built the same however. The <strong>new U8K boasts almost double the dimming zones compared to the U8H</strong>. The U8K makes for a solid gaming TV for the current generation PS5 and Xbox Series X gamers. That&#39;s because it comes equipped with a 120Hz refresh rate and HDMI 2.1.</p><h3>Samsung 980 Pro 2TB M.2 SSD $99.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-samsung-980-pro-placement" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Looking for a fast and inexpensive M.2 SSD from a brand that you recognize? Here&#39;s your answer. Today Amazon is offering the <a href="https://zdcs.link/jkyke">Samsung 980 Pro</a> 2TB PCIe 4.0 NVMe Gen 4 solid state drive for only $125.99. Compared to Western Digital and Seagate&#39;s out-of-the-box PS5 ready SSDs, this is the least expensive. In terms of performance, it&#39;s no longer the fastest SSD on the market (the <a href="https://zdcs.link/r0Pp5">990 Pro</a> is), but it&#39;s still a <strong>very</strong> fast drive. It certainly more than meets the minimum 5600MB/s speed requirement to be used as a PS5 storage upgrade, with speeds of up to 7,100MB/s.</p><h3>Officially Licensed WD SN850P 2TB PS5 SSD for $129.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-wd-black-sn850-ssd-v2" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>There are plenty of great deals on PS5-compatible SSDs. However, if you&#39;re looking for one that has been officially licensed by Sony, then your options just narrowed down to a single SSD. That&#39;s right, the <a href="https://zdcs.link/2XXWY">WD Black SN850P</a> is the only SSD that&#39;s officially licensed for the PS5. Today, Amazon has the 2TB model for the lowest price we&#39;ve ever seen. The WD SN850P was made specifically for the PS5 console. That means it fulfills all of Sony&#39;s requirements, like a minimum read speed of 5,500MB/s, a PCI-Express Gen4x4 interface, and a slim yet effective heatsink that fits within the confines of the PS5 bay. So what makes the SN850P any different from WD&#39;s flagship SN850X? Aesthetics aside, absolutely nothing. But that&#39;s not a bad thing. The SN850X is one of the fastest SSDs on the market. The SN850P is usually <em>more expensive</em> than the SN850X  and that&#39;s probably to cover the cost of the official PS5 licensing. So, you&#39;re getting the only licensed PS5 SSD on the market, and it happens to also be one of the fastest SSDs on the market, AND it&#39;s priced at an all time low. That&#39;s a win-win situation for any PS5 gamer.</p><h3>Fire TV Stick 4K Max for $24.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-fire-tv-stick-4k-max" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>As part of its Early Prime Day event, Amazon has its Fire TV Stick 4K Max for only $24.99, or 55% off the original retail price of $54.99. This is the best Fire TV stick that you can get. It has 40% more processing power than the original Fire TV stick, which means it can handle 4K Ultra HD, Dolby Vision, HDR, HDR10+, and Dolby Atmos audio without a hitch. It also supports the new Wi-Fi 6 standard to handle the increased bandwidth needed for those big 4K streams. This is better than a built-in smart TV interface because you can transfer it from TV to TV without having to redo all your profiles and settings.</p><h3>Alienware Aurora RTX 4090 Gaming PC for $2999.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-alienware-aurora-r15-2" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>As part of its Black Friday in July event, Dell is offering an <a href="https://zdcs.link/3ZZOK">Alienware Aurora R15</a> gaming PC equipped with the top-of-the-line GeForce RTX 4090 GPU for only $2999.99. The R15 is Alienware&#39;s latest flagship gaming PC, equipped with the newest AMD Ryzen 7 7700 processor with Cryo-Tech liquid cooling and an overpowered GeForce RTX 4090 GPU. The RTX 4090 is far and away the most powerful video card you can get right now, leaving competitors like AMD&#39;s latest Radeon RX 7900 XTX in the dust. It&#39;s also ridiculously more powerful than any of the RTX 30 series cards: it&#39;s up to 90% faster than the 3080 Ti. The 4090 is the one and only solution to ray-traced 4K gaming at consistent 60+fps. If you&#39;re still not convinced, check out our <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/nvidia-geforce-rtx-4090-founders-edition-review">RTX 4090 review</a>.</p><h3>Alienware m17 AMD Ryzen 9 6900HX RX 6850M XT Laptop for $1199.99</h3><p><em><strong>Equivalent to Intel Core i9-12900H with RTX 3080</strong></em></p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-alienware-m17-2" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>As part of its Dell Black Friday in July event, Dell is offering an <a href="https://zdcs.link/BJJDN">Alienware m17</a> 17&quot; gaming laptop equipped with the powerful AMD Ryzen 9 6900HX CPU and Radeon RX 6850M XT GPU for only $1299.99 after a $900 instant discount. That&#39;s an incredible price for the most powerful AMD gaming laptops around. The AMD Radeon RX 6850M XT is currently AMD&#39;s most powerful mobile GPU and its performance is comparable to NVIDIA&#39;s mobile RTX 3080/Ti. It will easily handle any game on the native 1080p display.</p><h3>Flexispot Electric Standing Desk for Under $159.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-sanodesk-standing-desks" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>For a limited time, Amazon is offering a <a href="https://zdcs.link/4PxkX">Flexispot 55&quot;x28&quot; Electric Standing Desk</a> with a single piece maple  desktop surface for only $159.99. It&#39;s originally $239.99, but there&#39;s a $20 coupon you can clip on the product page and an additional 25% off coupon code &quot;<strong>25L1D8JC</strong>&quot; that you will have to apply manually during checkout. Although we have seen less expensive standing desks, they are all smaller at about 48&quot;x24&quot;. The Flexispot desktop surface measures 55x28&quot;. The 1&quot; seamless desktop is sturdy enough to support up to 187 pounds, so people with heavy full-tower PCs and 48&quot; displays (like myself) won&#39;t have to worry. The legs are made of steel of support. The single electric motor lift mechanism offers height adjustment from 28&quot; to 47.6&quot;, at a speed of 1&quot; per second.</p><h3>Early Prime Day Deal: 3 Free Months of Audible Premium Plus</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-audible-premium-plus" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Amazon kicks off its Early Prime Day Deals event with one of the best subscription deals we&#39;re going to see for the entire month of July. Right now Amazon Prime members can get <a href="https://zdcs.link/GYDjx">3 free months of Audible Premium Plus membership</a>. Only new subscribers are eligible. You&#39;ll need to log into your Amazon Prime account to see this deal. If you&#39;re not sure whether or not you&#39;re eligible, simply click on the link; if you see the promo then you&#39;re eligible.</p><h3>2021 Apple iPad 10.2&quot; 64GB for $249.99</h3><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="apple-ipad-102-daily-deal" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Even at its $329 MSRP, the 2021 Apple iPad is $110 cheaper than the 2022 Apple iPad, $170 cheaper than the iPad Mini, $270 cheaper than the iPad Air, and $470 cheaper than the iPad Pro. Despite its low price tag, this is a fully featured and capable tablet. The Apple A13 Bionic chip offers very good CPU and GPU performance and the large 10.2-inch Retina display is bright and crisp. It&#39;s a great option for school, work, or simply relaxing with your favorite movie, book, or streaming service. iPad also features both a front-facing camera for voice chat, and rear camera for taking photos and videos.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/070623-1688680793328.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Early Prime Day Deal: The Most Affordable Apple iPad Is Now Even Cheaper]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/deal-alert-apple-ipad</link><description><![CDATA[Arrives before June 18]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 22:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">355b5c44-351a-4a5c-b937-12a96ae7541d</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Today Amazon is offering the 2021 <a href="https://zdcs.link/3jwwP">Apple iPad</a> 10.2&quot; Wi-Fi 64GB tablet for only $249.99 after an additional $29.01 discount that&#39;s automatically applied during checkout. This iPad normally retails for $329, so you&#39;re saving about 25%. This is the lowest price we&#39;ve ever seen for what was already the most affordable iPad you can get and I don&#39;t think it will get any cheaper for Prime Day.</p><h2>2021 Apple iPad 10.2&quot; 64GB for $249.99</h2><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="apple-ipad-102-daily-deal" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Even at its $329 MSRP, the 2021 Apple iPad is $110 cheaper than the 2022 Apple iPad, $170 cheaper than the iPad Mini, $270 cheaper than the iPad Air, and $470 cheaper than the iPad Pro. Despite its low price tag, this is a fully featured and capable tablet. The Apple A13 Bionic chip offers very good CPU and GPU performance and the large 10.2-inch Retina display is bright and crisp. It&#39;s a great option for school, work, or simply relaxing with your favorite movie, book, or streaming service. iPad also features both a front-facing camera for voice chat, and rear camera for taking photos and videos.</p><p>There&#39;s a <a href="https://zdcs.link/BJM51">new 2022 iPad</a> out, and guess what? Apple raised the base price to a whopping $440! Although the price increase could be justified by the substantial upgrades to the processor and display, that also means that 2021 was the last model year to have an economically priced iPad.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><h2>More Apple Deals</h2><ul><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/the-best-iphone-deals">The Best iPhone Deals</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-ipad-deals">The Best iPad Deals</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-airpods-deals">The Best AirPods Deals</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-apple-watch-deals">The Best Apple Watch Deals</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/the-best-macbook-deals">The Best MacBook Deals</a></li></ul><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/05/appleipadprimeday-1688586660321.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Run Rabbit Run Review]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/run-rabbit-run-review</link><description><![CDATA[Australian horror-thriller Run Rabbit Run is led by powerful performances, but wastes its “creepy kid” premise by playing its cards too close to the chest.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 21:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">cdb71e2a-e0c1-4d1e-bb4e-4d5e07294bd6</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Director Daina Reid crafts an impressive atmosphere in Run Rabbit Run, the Australian horror-thriller now streaming on Netflix. Led by an impressive performance from Succession’s Sarah Snook, Run Rabbit Run even comes close to entering the canon of great “creepy kid” movies, but despite all its bells and whistles, the  structure of its screenplay works against itself at every turn. The result is a scattered and often repetitive film that wastes its central premise, which isn’t even fully revealed until about 10 minutes before the end.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>After opening with a dreamlike sequence that has little symbolic bearing on the story, Run Rabbit Run paves the path for an unsettling domestic drama. As the blunt single mother Sarah (Snook) prepares for her lively daughter Mia’s (Lily LaTorre) seventh birthday party, a rabbit arrives at their doorstep at the same time as a birthday card from Sarah’s estranged mother, Joan. Sarah’s father has recently died, leaving a clutter of boxes for her to deal with and an emotional fog she can’t quite work through. This becomes all the more difficult when Mia, after insisting on keeping the rabbit, begins asking – and eventually, demanding – to visit Joan, despite never having met her or even being told her name.</p><section data-transform="image-with-caption" data-image-url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/runrabbitrun-netflix-095-1688678148031.jpg" data-image-title="Sarah Snook and Lily LaTorre in Run Rabbit Run" data-image-class="article-image-full-size" data-image-link="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/runrabbitrun-netflix-095-1688678148031.jpg" data-caption="Sarah%20Snook%20and%20Lily%20LaTorre%20in%20Run%20Rabbit%20Run" /></section><p>Mia’s odd behavior begins to escalate, between claiming that she “misses” Joan, and knowing intimate details and tidbits about Sarah’s deeply private past –a past that is kept largely hidden from the audience until late into the film). Sarah instinctively blames this mysterious knowledge on Mia’s father – finger-pointing which, in an act of fairly solid construction by screenwriter Hannah Kent, has the added effect of Sarah being unable to ask him for help when her parenting struggles eventually mount –  and she also balks at the idea of seeking professional help for Mia, or for herself, when the situation grows more concerning. </p><p>Most of the drama hinges on Snook’s striking performance, which becomes increasingly distraught as Mia wraps herself in her fantasies. Reid, in turn, crafts a number of subtleties throughout the movie’s first half:  frigid color correction, anticipation stoked by darkened negative spaces, the perfectly timed blowing of a white curtain the first time Mia jokingly mentions a ghost. The movie’s tensions continue to build, as Sarah discovers layer after layer to Mia’s seeming delusions. After a while, these setups largely lead to unsatisfying payoffs – if they’re paid off at all.</p><section data-transform="quoteBox">The structure of the screenplay works against itself at every turn</section><p>The key problem lies in the fact that the secrets of Sarah’s past are only secret to the audience. Every character in the film has significantly more information than we do, and the dramatic tension shared between Sarah and Mia – told through a mother’s concerned looks, as her daughter starts down an unconventional path – hinges on both characters knowing the full picture, or at least one of them trying to determine how much the other does or does not know. But given the opaqueness of the script, the audience is rarely allowed to empathize or connect with Sarah beyond the way she shuts Mia down every time the thorny subject is broached.  </p><p>Sarah’s prickliness is certainly engaging, but her less-than-stellar parenting ends up having no thematic ties to why she and her own mother are estranged (a dynamic seldom explored). After a while, what the film is even about becomes its own kind of mystery. Scenes quickly settle into a repetitive rhythm. Mia, after making outlandish claims, runs off as her mother gives chase, before something mildly spooky occurs – either in the corners of the frame, or entirely off screen – before the cycle begins again.</p><section data-transform="poll" data-id="f3849876-08a4-418a-8088-0abdddbf77a7"></section><p>These frustrations compound when the movie can’t seem to decide how to best visualize Mia’s invocations of the past, or to whose perspective the story should be tethered. It switches gears abruptly from creepy kid movie, to ghost story, to tale of a woman gone mad, but without letting any one of these horror modes linger long enough to make emotional sense. As each of these plots unfold, they end up playing out like parallel stories suddenly smashed together, their literal and symbolic elements rarely working in tandem, in a mish-mash movie whose impact is constantly undercut by its own indecisiveness.</p><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/run-rabbit-run-blogroll-1688678641935.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Erik Adams</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[San Diego Comic-Con Schedule Starts Rolling Out: Spider-Man 2, Pokémon, and More]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/san-diego-comic-con-schedule-starts-rolling-out-spider-man-2-pokemon-and-more</link><description><![CDATA[San Diego Comic-Con has just begun to roll out the schedule for its annual convention, and the first full day has the likes of Insomniac's Spider-Man 2, Prime Video's Wheel of Time, Max's Harley Quinn, and a Pokemon panel.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:56:28 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">881fe191-ec0f-4089-a6ea-45d98569450c</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>San Diego Comic-Con has just begun to roll out the schedule for its annual convention, and the first full day is looking pretty TV and game-heavy.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>There was some concern over just what would be arriving at the usually very buzzy Comic-Con, which announced<a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/marvel-phase-six-avengers-kang-dynasty-secret-wars"> Marvel Phases 5 and 6 just last year</a>. <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/marvel-skipping-san-diego-comic-con-hall-h-one-year-after-triumphant-return">Marvel will reportedly not be holding</a> panels this year, as well as Netflix, Universal, and Sony Pictures. The ongoing writers&#39; strike and potential actors&#39; strike have made planning more uncertain, especially as <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/sag-aftra-and-hollywood-studios-have-extended-negotiations-to-july-12">SAG-AFTRA extended its contract deadline</a> with Hollywood studios until July 12 - meaning we may not know if the organization will go on strike or not until just days before SDCC.</p><p>Even still, the first full day - Thursday, July 20 - is has some buzzy panels and appearances on the docket. Perhaps among the biggest is Insomniac Games&#39; Spider-Man 2, which is<a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/spider-man-2-san-diego-comic-con-panel"> getting the blockbuster treatment in Hall H</a>. Pokemon will also have its first SDCC panel that day.</p><p>On the TV side, Max will be there with animated series like Harley Quinn and Adventure Time: Fionna &amp; Cake, Prime will be bringing its fantasy adaptation Wheel of Time, and Peacock will show up with Twisted Metal. Paramount Pictures will also have a panel for Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem.</p><p>See the highlights below, which will be updated each day as Comic-Con releases its schedule. All times are in Pacific. For the complete schedule, <a href="https://www.comic-con.org/cci/thursday">click here.</a> </p><h2>Thursday</h2><p><strong>11:00am - 12:30pm - Max Original Animation: </strong>Max Original Animation celebrates new and returning animated series&#39; including an expansion in the Adventure Time universe, Adventure Time: Fionna &amp; Cake; a new animated series, Young Love, based on the characters from Matthew A. Cherry and Sony Pictures Animation’s Oscar-winning animated short, Hair Love; and a preview of the upcoming fourth season for the fan-favorite Harley Quinn. The panel will feature exclusive sneak peeks, surprise panelists, and more. Moderated by Damian Holbrook (TV Guide magazine).</p><p><strong>11:30am - 12:30pm - Paramount Pictures: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem</strong>: Paramount Pictures brings a panel discussion and footage presentation with filmmakers.</p><p><strong>11:45am - 12:45pm - Pokémon: Bringing Iconic Animation to Global Audiences</strong>: The Pokémon Company International (TPCi) takes a behind-the-scenes look at how the beloved Pokémon animated series is localized from its original Japanese version to one of the most popular series enjoyed by international audiences. In a panel moderated by streamer and comic book writer Meghan Camarena (also known as Strawburry17), TPCi&#39;s Taito Okiura (vice president of marketing and business development), Andy Gose (senior director of media production), and Hilary Thomas (senior producer) will discuss optimizing the series for global viewers, provide fans with a sneak peek at the special collection of episodes that will conclude Ash and his Pikachu&#39;s 25-season storied journey in Pokémon Ultimate Journeys: The Series, and share new behind-the-scenes insights regarding the highly anticipated Pokémon Horizons: The Series coming soon to fans around the world.</p><p><strong>12:45pm - 1:45pm - Ghosts</strong>: Ghosts, one of television’s top comedies on CBS and Paramount+, returns to Comic-Con after a season cliffhanger where Sam saw a piercing white light shoot from the heavens directly into their home. Please join us for a special Ghosts presentation.</p><p><strong>1:45pm - 2:45pm - Behind the Scenes with the Cast of Jury Duty</strong>: From producers of The Office, The White Lotus, and Bad Trip, the Amazon Freevee Original series Jury Duty chronicles the inner workings of an American jury trial through the eyes of one particular juror, Ronald Gladden, who doesn’t realize that everyone around him is an actor and the entire trial is fake. Get the inside scoop on what was happening behind the scenes during the making of the series from the cast and creative team, and meet San Diego’s own hometown hero, Ronald.</p><p><strong>2:00pm - 3:00pm - The Wheel of Time</strong>: The Wheel continues to turn at Comic-Con, as the cast of Prime Video’s hit series The Wheel of Time gives a sneak peek into the highly anticipated second season. In addition to a discussion about how the show is bringing Robert Jordan’s iconic book series from page to screen, they’ll be revealing exclusive season 2 content, as well as some other exciting surprises for attendees. Season 2 of The Wheel of Time will premiere on September 1.</p><p><strong>2:30pm - 3:30pm - Marvel’s Spider-Man 2: Symbiotic Relationships</strong>: Insomniac Games’ creative director Bryan Intihar, game director Ryan Smith, narrative director Jon Paquette, and senior art director Jacinda Chew are joined by actors Yuri Lowenthal (Peter Parker), Nadji Jeter (Miles Morales), Laura Bailey (Mary Jane Watson), and Tony Todd (Venom), along with VO and creative director Bill Rosemann from Marvel Games, to discuss the upcoming PlayStation 5 game. Get a behind-the-scenes look at Insomniac Games’ take on the monstrous Venom and how the symbiote plays a role in the sequel to the hit PlayStation games Marvel’s Spider-Man and Marvel’s Spider-Man: Miles Morales.</p><p><strong>3:00pm - 4:00pm - An Inside Look at Cruel Summer Season 2</strong>: The stars and creative team behind Freeform’s hit series Cruel Summer take you behind the scenes of season 2 and tease all the twists and turns viewers can expect from the shocking final episodes. Fans will be treated to an exclusive sneak peek of the rest of the season and a conversation with stars Lexi Underwood, Sadie Stanley, and Griffin Gluck, alongside executive producers Michelle Purple and Bill Purple. New episodes of Cruel Summer air Mondays at 10/9c on Freeform and stream next day on Hulu.</p><p><strong>3:15pm - 4:15pm - Peacock&#39;s Original Comedy Series Twisted Metal</strong>: Get an exclusive sneak peek at Peacock’s new original comedy series Twisted Metal. Based on the classic PlayStation game series, Twisted Metal is a high-octane action comedy based on an original take by Rhett Reese and Paul Wernick (Deadpool) and written by Michael Jonathan Smith (Cobra Kai), about a motor-mouthed outsider offered a chance at a better life, but only if he can successfully deliver a mysterious package across a post-apocalyptic wasteland. The ten-episode series stars Anthony Mackie, Stephanie Beatriz, Thomas Haden Church, with Will Arnett and Joe Seanoa, and guest stars Neve Campbell and streams only on Peacock on July 27.</p><p><strong>4:15pm - 5:15pm - A24&#39;s Talk to Me</strong>: Danny and Michael Philippou (a.k.a. RackaRacka) discuss their journey from YouTube creators to their feature debut and how their love of genre led them to make the most anticipated horror film of the summer. They will be joined by Talk to Me cast members Sophie Wilde, Joe Bird, Alexandra Jensen, and Zoe Terakes.</p><p><strong>4:30pm - 5:30pm - FX&#39;s What We Do in the Shadows</strong>: We’re sending ravens—500 ravens!—to invite you to join America’s favorite vampire roommates at Comic-Con! Be among the first humans to set eyes on a brand-new episode, complete with surprises! What We Do in the Shadows airs Thursdays at 10:00 ET/PT on FX, streaming the next day on Hulu. BAAAaaaaat!</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p><em>Thumbnail credit: JB Lacroix/Getty Images</em></p><p><em>Alex Stedman is a Senior News Editor with IGN, overseeing entertainment reporting. When she&#39;s not writing or editing, you can find her reading fantasy novels or playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons. </em></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="1080" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/sdcc-1688676961121.jpg" width="1920"/><dc:creator>Alex Stedman</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Nun 2 First Trailer Brings Back Taissa Farmiga and The Conjuring's Demon]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/the-nun-2-first-trailer-brings-back-taissa-farmiga-and-the-conjurings-demon</link><description><![CDATA[The Nun 2 trailer]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:34:40 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">f0349307-d848-4089-bd9d-58e975fba89c</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>The latest installment in the Conjuring Universe, The Nun 2, just dropped a doozy of a first trailer.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>You can check out the trailer below: </p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="the-nun-2-official-trailer" data-loop=""></section><p>Highlights from this first trailer include a demon hand bursting through a wall to grab a girl&#39;s head, a priest grimly explaining The Nun&#39;s origin, and a final shot that sees the Nun literally bursting from the pages of curiously arranged magazines. This first peek doesn&#39;t skimp on jump scares, either. </p><p>2018’s The Nun was a runaway commercial success, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/10/01/the-nun-is-now-the-highest-grossing-conjuring-movie-worldwide"><u>outperforming every other Conjuring </u></a>installment with a stunning $365.5 million box office haul. Despite its impressive box office numbers, though, the film received mostly negative reviews from critics. IGN’s Tom Jorgensen’s <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/09/05/the-nun-review"><u>5.5/10 review</u></a> called it “a good Conjuring history lesson wrapped in a mediocre horror movie.”</p><p>Taking place in 1952, the first film’s plot followed Sister Irene (Taissa Farmiga) as she dealt with a demonic nun (Bonnie Aarons). This time around, the story jumps forward to 1966 and finds Irene (again played by Farmiga) having to save her friend Maurice (Jonas Bloquet) from a demon. Storm Reid joins the cast as one of Irene’s allies. The Chronicles of Narnia’s Anna Popplewell portrays a character named Kate.</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/the-conjuring-the-devil-made-me-do-it">The Conjuring: The Devil Made Me Do It</a> director Michael Chaves helmed the sequel, working from a script by Ian Goldberg, Richard Naing, and Akela Cooper. James Wan and Peter Safran serve as co-producers. </p><p>The eight-film Conjuring franchise has grossed over $2 billion to date. Following The Nun 2 is <a href="https://collider.com/the-conjuring-4-last-rites-cast-crew-james-wan/"><u>The Conjuring: Last Rites</u></a>, the supposed final chapter of the Vera Farmiga and Patrick Wilson-led main story.</p><p>The Nun 2 will hit theaters on September 8.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p>Hayden Mears is an entertainment journalist who enjoys (you guessed it) entertainment. He also likes fitness boxing and writing bios in the third person.</p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/thenun2trailer-ign-blogroll1-1688661415448.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Hayden Mears</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deal Alert: The PS5 Officially Licensed WD Black SN850P 2TB SSD Is At Its Lowest Price Ever]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/deal-alert-ps5-officially-licensed-wd-black-sn850p-ssd</link><description><![CDATA[The only SSD with the right to have the PS5 logo on it]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">70c67230-08de-4a42-9be1-1d61dcbe744d</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>There are plenty of great deals on PS5-compatible SSDs. However, if you&#39;re looking for one that has been officially licensed by Sony, then your options just narrowed down to a single SSD. That&#39;s right, the <a href="https://zdcs.link/2XXWY">WD Black SN850P</a> is the only SSD that&#39;s officially licensed for the PS5. Today, Amazon has the 2TB model for the lowest price we&#39;ve ever seen.</p><h2>Officially Licensed WD SN850P 2TB PS5 SSD for $129.99</h2><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-wd-black-sn850-ssd-v2" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>The WD SN850P was made specifically for the PS5 console. That means it fulfills all of Sony&#39;s requirements, like a minimum read speed of 5,500MB/s, a PCI-Express Gen4x4 interface, and a slim yet effective heatsink that fits within the confines of the PS5 bay. Because it&#39;s officially licensed, the WD SN850P is the only SSD that&#39;s allowed to have the PS5 logo gloriously emblazoned. No, you&#39;ll never see it once it&#39;s installed and the PS5 is closed up and no, it won&#39;t make your PS5 any more special, but it&#39;s there.</p><p>So what makes the SN850P any different from WD&#39;s flagship SN850X? Aesthetics aside, absolutely nothing. But that&#39;s not a bad thing. The SN850X is one of the fastest SSDs on the market. The SN850X is the successor to the SN850 SSD, which was already fast enough to be PS5 compatible. The SN850X has newer flash chips (BiCS5 vs BiCS4) and an updated firmware, both of which offer improved sequential and random read/write speeds. For PC gamers, there&#39;s also an updated Game Mode 2.0 utility that&#39;s designed to tune the SSD for better performance during gaming sessions.</p><p>The SN850P is generally <em>more expensive</em> than the SN850X  and that&#39;s probably to cover the cost of the official PS5 licensing. But today, with this deal, the SN850P is <em>less expensive</em> than the SN850X. So, you&#39;re getting the only licensed PS5 SSD on the market, and it happens to also be one of the fastest SSDs on the market, AND it&#39;s priced at an all time low. That&#39;s a win-win situation for any PS5 gamer.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p>If you&#39;re looking for more SSD storage upgrade options for your PS5 console, check out our <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/the-best-ps5-ssd-deals-for-2023">best PS5 SSD deals of 2023</a>. There are even less expensive options if you&#39;re not married to any brand.</p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/04/wdblacksn850p-1688490149900.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deal Alert: The Alienware Aurora R15 RTX 4090 Gaming PC Has Dropped to $2999.99]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/alienware-r15-rtx-4090-gaming-pc</link><description/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">b42c304a-53a3-40e9-afb8-3973c3d8ccf8</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>As part of its Black Friday in July event, Dell is offering an <a href="https://zdcs.link/3ZZOK">Alienware Aurora R15</a> gaming PC equipped with the top-of-the-line GeForce RTX 4090 GPU for only $2999.99. We haven&#39;t seen an Alienware desktop equipped with an RTX 4090 for under $3K for a few months now. This is easily one of the most powerful gaming PCs you can get from Alienware and it&#39;s what you want if you want to play any game with every setting (including ray tracing) turned up in glorious 4K.</p><h2>Alienware Aurora RTX 4090 Gaming PC for $2999.99</h2><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-alienware-aurora-r15-2" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>The R15 is Alienware&#39;s latest flagship gaming PC, equipped with the newest AMD Ryzen 7 7700 processor with Cryo-Tech liquid cooling and an overpowered GeForce RTX 4090 GPU. Other specs include 16GB of DDR5-4800MHz RAM and a 1TB SSD. It&#39;s powered by a massive 1350W PSU that should handle anything you can throw at it, and a clear window side panel to show off your fancy RGB backlit internals.</p><p>The AMD Ryzen 7 7700X CPU boasts a max boost clock speed of 5.4GHz with 8 cores, 16 threads, and a 40MB cache. It&#39;s certainly a very capable processor for both workstation tasks and gaming. It can keep up with the newest Intel Raptor Lake Core i5 processors. It&#39;s cooled by a rather beefy 240mm all-in-one liquid cooler along with three system fans to manage ambient air temps. The upgraded Cryo-Tech edition (also included) offers even better thermal performance with a thicker radiator and better fans.</p><p>The RTX 4090 is far and away the most powerful video card you can get right now, leaving competitors like AMD&#39;s latest Radeon RX 7900 XTX in the dust. It&#39;s also ridiculously more powerful than any of the RTX 30 series cards: it&#39;s up to 90% faster than the 3080 Ti. The 4090 is the one and only solution to ray-traced 4K gaming at consistent 60+fps. If you&#39;re still not convinced, check out our <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/nvidia-geforce-rtx-4090-founders-edition-review">RTX 4090 review</a>.</p><p>This config retails for $3999.99, but we saw it for as low as $3149.99 on July 3. With the advent of July 4, Dell decided to drop the price another $150. If you&#39;re looking for a gaming PC that can crush any game currently out in 4K, then look no further than this deal right here.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><h2>For more gaming computer deals:</h2><ul><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/dell-black-friday-in-july-sale-alienware-gaming-laptops-and-pcs">Alienware Black Friday in July Sale</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/deal-alert-hp-4th-of-july-gaming-sale-save-on-omen-desktop-pcs-and-laptops">HP Black Friday in July Sale</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/deal-alert-lenovo-4th-of-july-gaming-sale-save-on-legion-desktop-pcs-and-laptops">Lenovo Black Friday in July Sale</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-gaming-pc-deals">The Best Gaming PC Deals Right Now (July 2023)</a></li><li><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/best-gaming-laptop-deals">The Best Gaming Laptop Deals Right Now (July 2023)</a></li></ul><p></p><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/04/alienwarer15-1688491095706.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Early Prime Day Deal: Get 3-Months of Audible Premium Plus for Free]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/amazon-prime-day-audible-membership-deal</link><description><![CDATA[This free Audible promotion is IGN's favorite early Amazon Prime Day deal for 2023. Here's how to get 3-months of Audible Premium Plus for free.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">a4ab8199-c1f6-4b29-938b-6d3266cdf61d</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>Amazon kicks off its Early Prime Day Deals event with one of the best subscription deals we&#39;re going to see for the entire month of July. Right now Amazon Prime members can get <a href="https://zdcs.link/GYDjx">3 free months of Audible Premium Plus membership</a>. Only new subscribers are eligible. You&#39;ll need to log into your Amazon Prime account to see this deal. If you&#39;re not sure whether or not you&#39;re eligible, simply click on the link; if you see the promo then you&#39;re eligible and if you don&#39;t then you&#39;re not.</p><h3>Early Prime Day Deal: 3 Free Months of Audible Premium Plus</h3><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-audible-premium-plus" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>Audible is a subscription service that gives you access to hundreds of thousands of audiobooks without ever having to purchase them. There are two paid membership plans: the lower tier Audible Plus ($7.95/mo) and the higher tier Audible Premium Plus ($14.95/mo). The biggest difference between the two is the size of the audiobook library. Whereas Audible Plus only lets you listen to a selection of about 10,000 audiobooks, the Audible Premium Plus plan gives you access to a whopping 500,000 audiobooks. These include all-time classics like Harry Potter, Game of Thrones (A Song of Ice and Fire), Witcher, The Sandman Series, The Lord of the Rings, Brandon Sanderson&#39;s The Stormlight Archives, Mistborn, and much more.</p><p>Although the seriously expanded library is the main draw of the Audible Premium Plus membership, there are some other nice perks as well. Every month Premium Plus members get to pick one audiobook to keep in their library indefinitely, even after the membership expires. Also, Premium Plus members can get 30% off any additional audiobooks they wish to purchase, in addition to exclusive limited-time discounts.</p><p>On any given day, new subscribers are eligible for a 30-day free trial of either Audible membership. The three month extended trial only happens 2-3 times per year. It&#39;s already happened once in February, and there&#39;s always one that&#39;s tied to Amazon Prime Day (which is this deal right here). If you forego this deal, you&#39;ll probably have to wait until Black Friday for your final shot at it this year.</p><h3>More Great Deals Before Prime Day</h3><p>There are plenty of other great deals to already check out before the big <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/amazon-prime-day-2023-dates-announced">Prime Day sale over July 11-12</a>. This includes <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/amazon-prime-day-music-unlimited-membership-deal">3-months of Amazon Music Unlimited for free</a>, 30% off the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/prime-day-deal-amazon-echo-buds-true-wireless-earphones">new Amazon Echo Buds (2023)</a>, and a whole selection of <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/prime-day-amazon-device-deals">Amazon devices</a> that have already seen discounts. Plus, we&#39;ve even got <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/10-things-you-need-to-know-before-amazon-prime-day-this-year">10 vital tips and tricks for you</a> to follow to ensure you save as much as possible this Prime Day. If you&#39;re trying to keep costs down while maintaining your favorite hobby, stay tuned for more incredible discounts or follow <a href="https://twitter.com/IGNDeals">@IGNDeals</a> on Twitter for even more updates before Prime Day.</p><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="best-deals-evergreen-articles-list" data-type="list"></section></p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p></p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/png" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/03/get-3-months-of-audible-for-free-prime-day-2023-best-deal-ign-reddit-1688393525058.png" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deal Alert: Buy a PS5 DualSense Edge Controller, Get a Bonus $75 Dell eGift Card]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/deal-alert-ps5-dualsense-edge-controller</link><description/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">00dbef56-1f3b-4da1-bc51-f5137c636fdb</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>As part of the Dell Black Friday in July event, Dell is offering a bonus $75 Dell eGift Card when you purchase a <a href="https://zdcs.link/2XXp5">PS5 DualSense Edge</a> controller for $199.99. That&#39;s easily the best deal we&#39;ve ever seen for this premium controller. The promotional gift card will be sent to your inbox within 20 days and you&#39;ll have 90 days thereafter to spend it. You can use it on pretty much anything at Dell.com, including gaming PCs and laptops, monitors, gaming consoles and video games, electronics, and more.</p><h3>PS5 DualSense Edge Controller for $199.99 Plus Bonus $75 Dell eGift Card</h3><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p><section data-transform="commerce-deal" data-slug="daily-deals-ps5-dualsense-edge" data-type="grid"></section></p><p>The DualSense Edge is Sony&#39;s high-end controller for the PS5 console. Like the Xbox Elite Series 2 controller, it offers pro-level features like grips, adjustable analog sticks, mappable rear buttons, profiles, and more. You can swap out the standard analog stick tops with convex replacements that come in two different heights. You have two different options for the back buttons: levers like in the Xbox Elite Series 2 or smaller nubs. One of the most important features of any pro controller are the triggers, and they’ve gotten attention in the DualSense Edge as well. Next to each trigger is a stop slider that lets you adjust how far you have to press the trigger down to make it register. You can choose standard, medium, or short travel distances, the better to get off quick shots in competitive shooters.</p><p>All this tech is housed in a hardshell case for easy storage and transport. The case even has a flap that lets you charge the controller while it’s in the case. A 9-foot USB-C charging cable is also included. Plus, if your analog sticks crap out, you can buy <a href="https://zdcs.link/mlX5y?_ga=721116655.1681141708">replacements for $19.99</a>. We liked it so much, we gave it a <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/dualsense-edge-review">9/10 review</a>.</p><section data-transform="divider"></section><p>Check out more of the best <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/dell-black-friday-in-july-sale-alienware-gaming-laptops-and-pcs">Dell Black Friday in July deals</a>.<br /><br />
</p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/06/13/ps5dualsenseedge-1686679601025.jpg" width="1280"/><dc:creator>Eric Song</dc:creator></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insidious: The Red Door Review]]></title><link>https://www.ign.com/articles/insidious-the-red-door-review</link><description><![CDATA[A satisfying conclusion to the Lambert family’s long nightmare journey into The Further, even if it relies too heavily on jump scares.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">60531d71-c214-4c1a-9001-24cdce81b7ca</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="article-page"><p>As Blumhouse’s first wholly original franchise, there’s always a sense of homecoming when we get a new Insidious movie – and after two <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2015/06/04/insidious-chapter-3-review">prequel</a> <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/01/03/insidious-the-last-key-review">chapters</a> that diverted attention to Lin Shaye’s medium Elise, this feeling permeates Insidious: The Red Door. Patrick Wilson returns to the series, as both an actor and a first-time director, and refocuses the action on the Lambert family, whose journeys into the atmospheric netherworld of The Further have left their strength as a unit broken. Coming full circle back to the Lamberts and pushing those characters to reckon with the effect the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2011/03/31/insidious-review">first</a> <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2013/09/13/insidious-chapter-2-review">two</a> films had on them provides The Red Door with fertile ground to stage a headier – if less terrifying – take on those bedrock Blumhouse movies.</p><section data-transform="mobile-ad-break"></section><p>The Red Door picks up nine years after the Lambert haunting with a slightly-altered version of Chapter 2’s ending: father and son astral projectors Josh (Patrick Wilson) and Dalton (Ty Simpkins) elect to have their memories of the first two movies – and of their abilities – wiped in an effort to prevent the hungry entities of The Further. But the blissful ignorance of that fade-to-white happy ending was short-lived: Though Josh and Dalton can’t remember any specifics, the psychological scarring of the Lipstick-Face Demon’s attacks fractured their family, with Josh in particular unable to express himself in the midst of a worsening brain fog. Dalton is similarly haunted, but a passion for art – a cute nod to his drawings from the first film – seems to have kept him on the rails. A death in the family and Dalton’s simultaneous departure for college puts great strain on the Lamberts, and this time of transition represents a chance for the entities of The Further to attempt to cross over into the living world once again.</p><section data-transform="ignvideo" data-slug="insidious-the-red-door-official-final-trailer" data-loop=""></section><p>In his directorial debut, Patrick Wilson strikes a franchise-best balance between family melodrama and how Insidious’ supernatural elements illustrate it. The Further has always been a charmingly lo-fi horror locale, but The Red Door feels like the first time it (and the entities which call it home) has been used effectively as microcosm for the character arcs being pushed along. Dalton’s art teacher (Hiam Abbass) encourages him to “sink further” into his subconscious as he works on his big project: a painting of a red door he’s seeing in his nightmares. As these trance-like sessions bring secrets about his connection to the spirit world bubbling to the surface, both Dalton’s relationship with Josh and the appetite of the restless spirits become more severe. This shared “sins of the father” storyline and journey towards reconciliation is a simple, but solid thematic base to root the evil entities’ hunger in, and is lent weight by Wilson and Simpkins’ earnest performances. As Dalton, Simpkins in particular has to walk a fine line between the predictable angst of an 18-year-old and the genuine suspicion with which he has to treat Wilson’s Josh.</p><p>By and large, Simpkins strikes this balance very well, and maintains a measure of vulnerability for a character who easily could’ve fallen into the “broody art kid” archetype. Josh is on a somewhat parallel track to Dalton in putting his demons to bed. Haunted by Further entities as a child himself, Josh always struggled to engage with the spectral attacks on his family, but his tendency to push through things without talking about them has fully caught up with him here. Compared to the boisterous family man of the first two movies, Wilson plays Josh as a harried husk in The Red Door, and shines in the moments where the character’s barely holding it together. The increased focus on depth for Josh and Dalton reduces Renai (Rose Byrne) and Foster (Andrew Astor) to sounding boards for the lead characters’ struggles, usually through over-the-phone exposition dumps that routinely drag down the pace.</p><section data-transform="quoteBox">Wilson’s horror chops are at their most fruitful during luxurious long takes</section><p>As director, Wilson’s horror chops are at their most fruitful during The Red Door’s luxurious long takes, and he’s able to sustain significant stretches of dread around that strength. For as famous as the Insidious films are for their jump scares, they’re usually at their best and most creative in the buildup to the fright, forcing us to stop trusting the corners of our eyes. The writing is on the wall for Josh as soon as he agrees to go into an MRI machine (great time for a pee break, claustrophobes) but Wilson uses smart edits and escalating panic in his performance to turn that screw for as long as is sustainable before paying it off with the inevitable punchline. Wilson pushes this sensibility during daylight scares too, with one early appearance of a spirit playing out in a single take that goes on for what feels like a full minute, re-establishing that creeping, creepy tone that has always been a calling card for the series. Being involved with the franchise since the beginning –  and a frequent collaborator of James Wan’s to boot – it shouldn’t be much of a surprise that Wilson is so attuned to the hallmarks of the Insidious movies, but his ability to execute on them so confidently gives The Red Door an identity consistent with what Wan did in Insidious and Insidious: Chapter 2, all while better illuminating the drama. </p><p>Of course, these marathon, dread-filled rides to the top of the roller coaster often pay off with cacophonous outbursts of demonic rage or ghostly malcontent, punctuated by discordant string hits, and the potency of those moments is one area where The Red Door suffers from the law of diminishing returns. There’s a glut of jump scares throughout the movie, and not always as the result of minutes of carefully layered tension and misdirection. There’s an ugly scratch across my notepad that will attest to the raw power these moments can have out of the blue, but scant few of The Red Door’s attempts at frightening you feel like they’re iterating or innovating in a substantial way.</p><section data-transform="poll" data-id="4ab95b43-003c-4de6-9f13-b20c585432cd"></section><p>While Wilson has no problem mining the Lambert family drama for interpersonal conflict, The Red Door’s college setting feels comparatively nondescript. Though we get spooky moments in expected arenas – a classroom, a dorm room, a frat house – little of the activity feels specifically tied to Dalton’s college experience, and so doesn’t connect as cleanly as the family-themed horror does. With images of alcohol-poisoned ghost kids crawling after Dalton – maybe ones who had upbringings as affecting as his – The Red Door hints at more complex avenues it could&#39;ve explored using its college trappings, a more frank look at how Dalton relates to these kids who’ve died in tragedy. It seems that thread would’ve required one less Lambert to really home in on. </p><p>A new setting does mean a new opportunity to explain old information, and Dalton’s roommate Chris (Sinclair Daniel) serves as a refreshingly down-to-earth foil in that role. How quickly Chris is willing to accept Dalton’s astral powers and the resultant paranormal activity calls to mind Insidious&#39; bumbling ghost hunters Specs and Tucker. With Dalton now the relative expert on the subject, Chris’ matter-of-fact reactions and willingness to roll with punches for her new friend provide The Red Door with a reliable levity when needed.</p></section>]]></content:encoded><media:content height="1080" type="image/jpeg" url="https://assets-prd.ignimgs.com/2023/07/06/insidious-blogroll-1688658171691.jpg" width="1920"/><dc:creator>Erik Adams</dc:creator></item></channel></rss>